Mark Jones O. Solano

Software Developer

Philippines, Digos City, Davao del Sur

) +639369067328

mjsolano12345@gmail.com

https://mjsolano.me

• https://github.com/mjsol12

SUMMARY

I'm a software developer in the Philippines and a part of a team based in Belfast, I have doing heavy front-end using JavaScript and Typescript as my primary Language and some framework and library especially Angular and all its version, React, NodeJS and, MongoDB as my experienced database handle and data structuring, I have practiced myself to a quality of Development Standard and Ethics in coding as universal.

Throughout the years I have been employing myself to be the best of my self and the best of my current industry. I've never stop in improving myself and seek for better knowledge to get what is necessary in my line of work.

Relevant Experience

CasedDimensions Software Development Company

Software Developer: June 2020 - Present

- Rewarded for fixing a lot of bugs during my first 2 months in the job
- Front-end Development with Angular and React,
 Nodejs, and Azure DevOps
- Implements user story or feature
- Fixing bugs and design markups and methods
- Collaborate with colleague on the project implementation and a scrum methodology

DominOff- Freelancer and startup

Full Stack Developer: 2017 - Present

- Created a mobile app for client specification using NativeScript
- Heavy in Fron-end using Angular but also worked in back-end using Express and NodeJS
- Designed a data using Mongodb and Nodejs for API requirements
- Collaborate with project partners/developer for the implementation of system
- Provides client support and gradually seeing client for updates and support tech
- Integrated SMS/GSM data converter into web data

Kodaris - The Supply Chain Platform

Angular Developer(a month Part-time): Jan 2022 - Feb 2022

- Front-end Development with Angular
- Fixed Few bugs and submitted few PR implementing tickets
- Collaborate with colleague scrum methodology

Featured Skills

Programming Languages

Javascript(ES6), Typescript, Html, Css/Sass

Library & Framework

Angular, React, Nodejs, ExpressJS, Nativescript, MongDB

Tools

Git, Bitbucket, Github, Azure DevOps, Jira, Basics Remote Virtual Machine

Design

Bootstrap, Material UI, Material Design, Angular Material, Angular Design and Others

Education

2012-2016: BS Criminology Polytechnic College of Davao del Sur

Interest

Travel, Motorcycling, Reading